Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
- National Treasury Employees Union, Publication (Box 611, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: We have always been proud of our ability to serve our union members and are constantly researching new concepts that meet our specifications for quality and soncumer value, 1986; Publication (Box 611, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: In accordance with NTEU's commitment to provide its members the highest possible level, 1982; Publication (Box 611, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Position paper: AIDS in the Federal Workplace, 1988; Publication (Box 611, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Position paper: AIDS in the Federal Workplace, 1988; Publication (Box 611, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: First Time Offered: NTEU Prescription Eyewear Program, 1979; Publication (Box 611, Folder 6)
- New York Typographical Union No. 6, Publication (Box 612, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws, 1988; Publication (Box 612, Folder 1)
    Author: New York Typographical Union No. 6
  - Item 2: Constitution and by-laws, 1991; Publication (Box 612, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Scale of prices for Book and Job Work, 1983; Publication (Box 612, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Scale of prices for Book and Job Work, 1983; Publication (Box 612, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Contract and scale of prices; Newspaper branch, 1984; Publication (Box 612, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Memorandum of agreement between the New York Times Company and New York Typographical Union No. Six, 1987-1993 (Box 612, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Memorandum of agreement between the New York Times Company and New York Typographical Union No. Six, 1987-1993 (Box 612, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Agreement between Keith Clark, Sidney, New York and Sidney Typographical Union No. 81, Sidney, New York: December 7, 1992 - December 3, 1995, 1992-1995 (Box 612, Folder 1)
    Author: Keith Clark; Sidney Typographical Union No. 81
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Official Directory, 1975; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
    Author: ITU (International Typographical Union)
    Notes: August, 1975
  - Item 2: Official Directory, 1975; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
    Notes: August, 1975. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Official Directory, 1976; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
    Notes: August, 1976
  - Item 4: Official Directory, 1977; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
    Notes: August, 1977
  - Item 5: Official Directory, 1978; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
    Notes: August, 1978
  - Item 6: Official Directory, 1979; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
    Notes: January, 1979.
  - Item 7: Official Directory, 1979; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
    Notes: January, 1979. Copy 2.
  - Item 8: Official Directory, 1980; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Official Directory, 1980; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
    Notes: August, 1980. Copy 2.
  - Item 10: Official Directory, 1981; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Official Directory, 1981; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
    Notes: July, 1981. Copy 2
  - Item 12: Official Directory, 1982; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Official Directory, 1982; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
    Notes: July, 1982. Copy 2
  - Item 14: Official Directory, 1984; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
    Notes: January, 1984.
  - Item 15: Official Directory, 1984; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
    Notes: July, 1984.
  - Item 16: Official Directory, 1985; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
    Notes: July, 1985.
  - Item 17: Official Directory, 1986; Publication (Box 612, Folder 2)
    Notes: July, 1986.
- ITU (International Typographical Union), Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Typographical Journal: Annual Report of the Officers, 1983; Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.182:no.3 (1983:Mar.)
  - Item 2: Typographical Journal: Annual Report of the Officers, 1983; Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.182:no.3 (1983:Mar.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Typographical Journal: Official Notice of Referendum, 1986; Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.189:no.2 (1986:Aug.)
  - Item 4: Minimum wages and hours data, 1976; Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
    Notes: July, 1976.
  - Item 5: Minimum wages and hours data, 1979; Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Agreement between Keith Clark, Sidney, New York and Sidney Typographical Union No. 81, Sidney, New York: December 4, 1989 - December 6, 1992, 1989-1992 (Box 612, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Agreement for Merger/Affiliation, 1986; Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
    Author: ITU (International Typographical Union); CWA (Communications Workers of America)
  - Item 8: Official Notice of Referendum, 1984; Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Member letter, 1977; Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
    Author: ITU (International Typographical Union) No. 6, Political Action Committee
  - Item 10: Review, 1978; Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.12:no.13 (1978:July 20)
  - Item 11: Union Membership is a family business, Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Printing plant employees: your right to organize, bargain collectively, Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: ITU provides more and better, Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Job security, Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
  - Item 15: What the ITU General Laws mean to you, Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
  - Item 16: An introduction to the ITU, Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
  - Item 17: What ITU membership can do for you, Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
  - Item 18: What is A Union?, 1978; Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
  - Item 19: What is A Union?, 1978; Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
  - Item 20: The Committee for Merger NOW!, 1984; Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
  - Item 21: The Committee for Merger NOW!, 1984; Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
  - Item 22: The Committee for Merger NOW!, 1984; Publication (Box 612, Folder 3)
- United Labor Unions, Publication (Box 612, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: United Labor News, 1980; Publication (Box 612, Folder 4)
    Author: United Labor Unions
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1980:Oct.)
    Language: English;Spanish.
  - Item 2: United Labor News, 1980; Publication (Box 612, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1980:Oct.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: United Labor News, 1981; Publication (Box 612, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1981:Jan.)
  - Item 4: United Labor News, 1981; Publication (Box 612, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1981:Jan.). Copy 2.
- Federation of University Employees, Publication (Box 612, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: By-laws and rules of order, Publication (Box 612, Folder 5)
    Author: Federation of University Employees. Local No. 35
  - Item 2: Agreement between Federation of University Employees, Local No. 35, AFL-CIO and Yale University, New Haven, Connecticut: July 10, 1974, Publication (Box 612, Folder 5)
    Author: Federation of University Employees
  - Item 3: Agreement between Yale University & Local 34, Federation of University Employees., 1985; Publication (Box 612, Folder 5)
    Author: Federation of University Employees. Local 34
- American Association of University Professors, Publication (Box 612, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Memorandum of understanding between the Board of Trustees and Faculty of Belleville Area College, 1980-1983 (Box 612, Folder 6)
    Author: Belleville Area College
  - Item 2: Agreement between Curry College and Curry College AAUP, Publication (Box 612, Folder 6)
    Author: Curry College; American Association of University Professors
  - Item 3: Collective bargaining agreement between Connecticut State University, American Association of University Professors and the Board of Trustees for Connecticut State University: August 24, 1990-August 19, 1993, 1990-1993 (Box 612, Folder 6)
    Author: Central Connecticut State University; Western Connecticut State University; Eastern Connecticut State University; Southern Connecticut State University; American Association of University Professors
  - Item 4: Collective bargaining agreement between Connecticut State University, American Association of University Professors and the Board of Trustees for Connecticut State University: August 24, 1990-August 19, 1993, 1990-1993 (Box 612, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Collective bargaining agreement between Connecticut State University, American Association of University Professors and the Board of Trustees for Connecticut State Colleges: In the interests of the Citizenry of Connecticut, 1979-1981 (Box 612, Folder 6)
- American Association of University Professors, Publication (Box 613, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Agreement between the State of New York and United University Professions: 1985-1988 (Box 613, Folder 1)
    Author: United University Professions (Association: N.Y.)
  - Item 2: Agreement between Temple University of the Commonwealth System of Higher Education and the American Association of University Professors, Temple Chapter: July 1, 1976-June 30, 1980, 1976-1980 (Box 613, Folder 1)
    Author: Temple University; American Association of University Professors
  - Item 3: Agreement between Temple University of the Commonwealth System of Higher Education and the American Association of University Professors, Temple Chapter: July 1, 1980-June 30, 1982, 1980-1982 (Box 613, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Agreement between Temple University of the Commonwealth System of Higher Education and the American Association of University Professors, Temple Chapter: July 1, 1980-June 30, 1982, 1980-1982 (Box 613, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Agreement between Western Michigan Unversity and the W.M.U. Chapter of the American Association of University Professors for September 24, 1981-September 5, 1984, 1981-1984 (Box 613, Folder 1)
    Author: Western Michigan University; American Association of University Professors
  - Item 6: Agreement between Bloomfield College and the Bloomfield College Chapter of the American Association of University Professors, July 1, 1981-June 30, 1983, 1981-1983 (Box 613, Folder 1)
    Author: Bloomfield College; American Association of University Professors
  - Item 7: Agreement between Rider College and the Rider College Chapter of the American Association of University Professors, 1976- 1979 (Box 613, Folder 1)
    Author: Rider College; American Association of University Professors
- American Association of University Professors, Publication (Box 613, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution of the Association, 1989; Publication (Box 613, Folder 2)
    Author: American Association of University Professors
  - Item 2: AAUP New York Conference, 1978; Publication (Box 613, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (1978:Dec.)
  - Item 3: Agreement between Western Michigan Unversity and the W.M.U. A.A.U.P. Chapter, October 24, 1978-September 1, 1981, 1978- 1981 (Box 613, Folder 2)
    Author: American Association of University Professors; Western Michigan University
  - Item 4: Agreement between Wilberforce University and Wilberforce University Faculty Association: effective October 8, 1979 through August 31, 1981, 1979-1981 (Box 613, Folder 2)
    Author: Wilberforce University Faculty Association; Wilberforce University
  - Item 5: Agreement between Board of Control Northern Michigan Unversity and American Association of University Professors, Northern Michigan University Chapter: July 1, 1980-June 30, 1983, 1980-1983 (Box 613, Folder 2)
    Author: Northern Michigan University; American Association of University Professors
  - Item 6: Agreement between Western Michigan Unversity and the W.M.U. Chapter of the American Association of University Professors for September 6, 1993-September 6, 1996, 1993-1996 (Box 613, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Agreement between Wayne State Unversity and the Wayne State University Chapter of the American Association of University Professors: July 1, 1978 to July 31, 1981, 1978-1981 (Box 613, Folder 2)
    Author: Wayne State University; American Association of University Professors
  - Item 8: Agreement between the State of New York and United University Professions: 1982-1985 (Box 613, Folder 2)
    Author: UUP (United University Professions)
- American Association of University Professors, Publication (Box 613, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Footnotes, 1984; Publication (Box 613, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1984:Fall)
  - Item 2: Your introduction to the American Association of University Professors, Publication (Box 613, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: AAUP, 1985; Publication (Box 613, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: AAUP: Advancing the Interests of the Profession with Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 613, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: AAUP: Advancing the Interests of the Profession with Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 613, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: AAUP: Advancing the Interests of the Profession with Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 613, Folder 3)
    Notes: Flyer. Copy 3.
  - Item 7: Agreement between United University Professions and the State of New York: 1991-1995 (Box 613, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Agreement between the State of New York and United University Professions: 1988-1991 (Box 613, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Agreement between the State of New York and United University Professions, Inc.: 1977-1979 (Box 613, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Agreement between the State of New York and United University Professions, Inc.: 1979-1982 (Box 613, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Agreement between the State of New York and United University Professions, Inc.: 1979-1982 (Box 613, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Memoranda of understanding relating to evaluation and promotion systems for Professional Employees, 1979; Publication (Box 613, Folder 3)
- UIU (Upholsterers' International Union of North America), Publication (Box 613, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: General laws of the Upholsterers' International Union of North America, 1982; Publication (Box 613, Folder 4)
    Author: UIU (Upholsterers' International Union of North America)
  - Item 2: General laws of the Upholsterers' International Union of North America, 1984; Publication (Box 613, Folder 4)
    Notes: Cover only in both English and French
- UIU (Upholsterers' International Union of North America), Publication (Box 613, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: U.I.U manual for U.I.U. Local Union Officers, Publication (Box 613, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: U.I.U manual for U.I.U. Local Union Officers, Publication (Box 613, Folder 5)
- UIU (Upholsterers' International Union of North America), Publication (Box 614, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: U.I.U manual for U.I.U. Shop Stewards and Shop Grievance Committees, Publication (Box 614, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: U.I.U manual for U.I.U. Shop Stewards and Shop Grievance Committees, Publication (Box 614, Folder 1)
- Utility Workers Union of America, Publication (Box 614, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Public Service Electric and Gas Company, on behalf of its Commercial Offices and Customer Payment Processing Center and Utility Co-Workers' Association: effective May 1, 1977, Publication (Box 614, Folder 2)
    Author: Utility Co-Workers Association; Public Service Electric and Gas Company
  - Item 2: Agreement between Public Service Electric and Gas Company, on behalf of its Commercial Offices and Customer Payment Processing Center and Utility Co-Workers' Association: effective May 1, 1977, Publication (Box 614, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Working agreement Consumers Power Company and Utility Workers Union of America affiliated with the AFL-CIO: covering Operating, Maintenance and Construction Employees: September 1, 1974 to September 1, 1977, 1974-1977 (Box 614, Folder 2)
    Author: Consumers Power Company (Mich.); Utility Workers Union of America
- Utility Workers Union of America, Publication (Box 614, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Collective bargaining contract between Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc. and the Utility Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO and its Local Union No. 1: effective August 19, 1983 through June 17, 1986 and thereafter as provided, 1983-1986 (Box 614, Folder 3)
    Author: Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc.; Utility Workers Union of America
- Utility Workers Union of America, Publication (Box 614, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Boston Edison Company and the Utility Workers Union of America, A.F.L.-C.I.O. and Local No. 369, U.W.U.A., A.F.L.-C.I.O.: Production and Maintenance Unit: Dated:, 1983; Publication (Box 614, Folder 4)
    Author: Boston Edison Company; Utility Workers Union of America
- Utility Workers Union of America, Publication (Box 614, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Agreement between Boston Edison Company and the Utility Workers Union of America, A.F.L.-C.I.O. and Local No. 387, U.W.U.A., A.F.L.-C.I.O.: Production and Maintenance Unit: Dated:, 1983; Publication (Box 614, Folder 5)
- Utility Workers Union of America, Publication (Box 614, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Collective bargaining contract between Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc. and the Utility Workers' Union of America, AFL-CIO and its Local Union No. 1-2: June 25, 1989 through June 20, 1992, 1989-1992 (Box 614, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Collective bargaining contract between Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc. and the Utility Workers' Union of America, AFL-CIO and its Local Union No. 1-2: June 15, 1986 through June 24, 1989, 1986-1989 (Box 614, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Collective bargaining contract between Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc. and the Utility Workers' Union of America, AFL-CIO and its Local Union No. 1: effective August 19, 1983 through June 17, 1986 and thereafter as provided, 1983-1986 (Box 614, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Working agreement Consumers Power Company and Utility Workers Union of America affiliated with the AFL-CIO: covering Operating, Maintenance and Construction Employees: September 1, 1980 to September 1, 1983, 1980-1983 (Box 614, Folder 6)
    Author: Consumers Power Company; Utility Workers Union of America
  - Item 5: Working agreement Consumers Power Company and Utility Workers Union of America affiliated with the AFL-CIO: covering Operating, Maintenance and Construction Employees: September 1, 1977 to September 1, 1980, 1977-1980 (Box 614, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Working agreement Consumers Power Company and Utility Workers Union of America affiliated with the AFL-CIO: covering Operating, Maintenance and Construction Employees: September 1, 1980 to September 1, 1983, 1980-1983 (Box 614, Folder 6)
- Utility Workers Union of America, Publication (Box 614, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Collective bargaining contract between Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc. and the Utility Workers' Union of America, AFL-CIO and its Local Union No. 1-2: effective June 18, 1980 through June 17, 1983 and thereafter as provided, 1980-1983 (Box 614, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Collective bargaining contract between Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc. and the Utility Workers' Union of America, AFL-CIO and its Local Union No. 1-2: effective June 18, 1977 through June 17, 1980 and thereafter as provided, 1977-1980 (Box 614, Folder 7)
- Utility Workers Union of America, Publication (Box 615, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Facts you should know about the Utility Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 615, Folder 1)
    Author: Utility Workers Union of America
  - Item 2: Facts you should know about the Utility Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 615, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Facts you should know about the Utility Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 615, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Be 2 steps ahead of the un-expected, 1986; Publication (Box 615, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Constitution, 1987; Publication (Box 615, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Constitution, 1991; Publication (Box 615, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Constitution, 1995; Publication (Box 615, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Agreement between the Detroit Edison Company and Local Union No. 223 of the Utility Workers Union of America: affiliated with the AFL-CIO: signed June 26, 1975, Publication (Box 615, Folder 1)
    Author: Utility Workers Union of America; Detroit Edison Company
- Wood, Wire and Metal Lathers' International Union, Publication (Box 615, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1973; Publication (Box 615, Folder 2)
    Author: Wood, Wire and Metal Lathers' International Union
- International Woodworkers of America, Publication (Box 615, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1989; Publication (Box 615, Folder 3)
    Author: International Woodworkers of America
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1991; Publication (Box 615, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Constitution, 1993; Publication (Box 615, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Structural organization, 1976; Publication (Box 615, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Wage and benefit gains, 1915-1976 (Box 615, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: The IWA Research and Education Department, Publication (Box 615, Folder 3)
    Author: Roy A. Ockert
  - Item 7: This letter is a means to explain to our membership the status of our health, 1982; Publication (Box 615, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: The energy dilemma what it means to jobs, Publication (Box 615, Folder 3)
    Author: R. Denny Scott
  - Item 9: Questions and Answers about the International, Publication (Box 615, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Labor & Log exports, Publication (Box 615, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: History of the International Woodworkers of America., 1977; Publication (Box 615, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Average Membership for 1976, 1977; Publication (Box 615, Folder 3)
- Workmen's Circle, Publication (Box 615, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Constitution, 1988; Publication (Box 615, Folder 4)
    Author: Workmen's Circle
  - Item 2: Constitution, 1994; Publication (Box 615, Folder 4)
    Notes: Cover only in both English and Yiddish
- National Writers Union, Publication (Box 615, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Memorandum of agreement, 1992; Publication (Box 615, Folder 5)
    Author: Writers Guild of America
  - Item 2: Memorandum of agreement, 1992; Publication (Box 615, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: A contract between the National Writers Union and the Black Film Review on a Code of Practices, 1986-1988 (Box 615, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Agreement, 1988-1990 (Box 615, Folder 5)
    Author: National Writers Union; Columbia University
  - Item 5: Agreement between National Writers Union and in these times, 1986; Publication (Box 615, Folder 5)
    Author: National Writers Union
  - Item 6: Agreement between Los Angeles Local, 1986-1988 (Box 615, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Contract between the National., 1986-1988 (Box 615, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Writers Guild of America: 1988 Theatrical and Television: Basic Agreement: effective August 8, 1988 through May 1, 1992, 1988- 1992 (Box 615, Folder 5)
- Writers Guild of America, Publication (Box 615, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Constitution and by-laws, 1986; Publication (Box 615, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Schedule of minimums, 1993; Publication (Box 615, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Schedule of minimums, 1993; Publication (Box 615, Folder 6)
- Writers Guild of America, Publication (Box 615, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: On Writing - 1993, Publication (Box 615, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Why I write in New York, 1992; Publication (Box 615, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Where we came from: a brief history of the Writers Guild of America, East and West, Publication (Box 615, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Agency List, 1992; Publication (Box 615, Folder 7)
    Notes: January 1, 1992.
  - Item 5: Script Registration Service, Publication (Box 615, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: Writers Guild of America is a labor union representing, Publication (Box 615, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: The Guild represents writers primarily for the purpose of collective bargaining, Publication (Box 615, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: This is in reply to your request, Publication (Box 615, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: Book price list, Publication (Box 615, Folder 7)
    Author: Naomi Silverman
- Writers Guild of America, Publication (Box 615, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Guild functions and services, Publication (Box 615, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Code of working rules, Publication (Box 615, Folder 8)